{
    "subject": "resource/Rob_Brydon's_Annually_Retentive",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Jane_Moore",
    "human_readable": "Jane Moore stars in Rob Brydon's Annually Retentive.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.953188955783844,
            "question": "Who stars in Rob Brydon's Annually Retentive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5111110806465149,
            "question": "What is the name of the show starring Jane Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46965470910072327,
            "question": "Is Rob Brydon an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4571532607078552,
            "question": "Who created the show 'Annually Retentive'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45411208271980286,
            "question": "What year was 'Annually Retentive' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41462162137031555,
            "question": "Where can you watch 'Annually Retentive'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3640657663345337,
            "question": "Are there any other notable actors in the show besides Jane Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3473568558692932,
            "question": "What genre is 'Annually Retentive' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28090721368789673,
            "question": "What makes 'Annually Retentive' unique compared to other comedy shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25128844380378723,
            "question": "Has Rob Brydon been involved in any other successful comedy shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jane Moore stars in Rob Brydon's Annually Retentive.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3436_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes 'Annually Retentive' unique compared to other comedy shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3436_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'Annually Retentive' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3436_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable actors in the show besides Jane Moore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3436_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3436_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as there are multiple mentions of Jane Moore being a guest on Rob Brydon's Annually Retentive."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Rob Brydon plays the reluctant host of a new history based panel show - Annually Retentive\" and also list \"Rob Brydon, Jane Moore\" as stars in \"Rob Brydon's Annually Retentive,\" which supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}